Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski. In this episode, I want
to show you how you can use AI to create
apps and some of the ways that are
working with AI that's really
gamechanging right now in the industry
and things that are just revolutionary.
I know a lot of coaches and mentors,
they have ideas for creating apps and
things like that. And there's tools that
are out there for doing them that you
don't even need to use AI or you don't
even need to know how to be pro a
programmer to be able to do this. And so
I want to show you some of those
different tools that are out there. Um
some of my favorite ones that you can
use, the ones that in the coaching
industry are used for creating apps. One
that I think a lot of people reference,
I' I've had clients that have used it.
I've not personally used it, but I've
heard great things about is Passion.io.
Um, I think it's one of the coolest
platforms that's out there for making a
simple coaching app for your coaching
business um that you can put together.
You can load up your coaching and things
like that. And the the the pricing is
very reasonable as far as how to build
it. It's not cheap, but it's reasonable
to put it together to be able to do
this. So like if you want to make
something specifically for your coaching
business, this is probably one of the
best ones that are out there. Now
Kajjabi and uh Thinkic, they do have
apps that are built into their
platforms. So, if you're using one of
these platforms in your business, you
know, they they do have a kind of like
an app builder type of a thing that you
can use to create an app that your
clients can use. Now, it's not
necessarily made for an app building
thing, but they are, let me see, branded
mobile app. Yeah, it's right here. See?
So, your brand mobile app get started
for free part of the $200 a month plan
that they have. So, yeah, Kajjabi has
this. So does Think Ific. That's not
Think Ific. That's a competitor.
Think ific right here. So Think Ific
also does have like a like a mobile app
type of thing for that for coaching that
you can do, which is which is pretty
cool. The ability to be able to do that
and to put that together. Um I think is
Yeah. Branded mobile right here. Yep.
Your brand on mobile. Now I use Thinkic,
but I don't even use their branded
mobile app thing. I just I've not done
that. Uh maybe I'll explore it. Maybe
I'll look into it and see if that's
something I want to do, but that's not
necessarily something that that I would
say put together. Now, let's say that
you want to build an AI app. Um
like an AI of yourself. We've done this
with a couple of different clients.
Deli.ai
allows you to upload your content to
create an AI of you. And there's these
other different mentors, coaches, and
stuff like that that you can see the
examples of how they've used it to put
it together.
Uh Cody. Chat is right here. You can
chat with her. You can call her and it
it gives you an example of kind of what
it's like to be able to do this. You can
you can talk to it.
What's up? How are you? So, it's like
it's also she's also using it to promote
her live workshops, her her offers and
things like that. So, it's acting as
kind of a lead generation tool for her
business um to talk to this digital
version and it has like a
>> Hey, I'm good. Well, as good as a
digital version of me can be. What about
you? What's on
>> So, that's pretty cool. Is is that
right there? Now, there's some other
more advanced tools that are out there,
and this is what I really was excited to
show you is one of them called
replet.com.
replet.com
has what they call agent3
that's built into it and you can use it
to create
just about any app that you could
imagine. I want to show you kind of
their their homepage for their offer
here.
replet.com has your hosting. It has all
of that. And this is more like if you
want to create a tool or something or an
app or even like a a video game or
things like that, you could use Replet
to be able to do this. It's a very
advanced tool, but they have their agent
3, an autonomous agent. It's like chat
GPT, but it actually goes in and it
builds all the code and everything like
that. This is a lot more advanced. Um,
but if you learn how to use this, this
is really incredible to be able to put
together. Um, where you can create stuff
like that. Now, you could actually
design your app in a tool called Figma
right here. And Figma has AI built into
it as well, where you can type in, you
know, what you want to create. It will
create a design for you for any kind of
tool or app that you could think of.
This is just going to create kind of the
design of the layout of the app, but
it's really high quality as far as that
goes. Uh there's another one that's out
there called V0ero that kind of does
similar. This one creates like designs
for your apps and things like that. So
these are just different um types of
apps that you could create. And what you
do is you literally type in okay what
what I want to create and it will go
ahead and it will start to create it for
you. And all of them work very similar
like this is how you would do it. I want
to create a clone of Super Mario
Brothers that I can use generate
graphics and images
and create
functionality like this is literally you
could start with that type of an of a
prompt. Super Mario Brothers is a is a
video game
and so it'll go ahead and it'll plan it
and then it'll actually build it and you
don't have to know how to code anything.
and you just tell it what functionality
that you want and it will put it all
together and then it can do the hosting
for you. So, it's a really really cool
uh platform. I want to show you just a
couple of examples of how I've used it
just just playing around a little bit.
Um I've created a number of different
little micro
projects with it. Um,
just just as an example, let me see.
I made like an idea. This was like a
year ago. I actually did this. It was
this idea generator
right here. It generates ideas for your
business. Um,
see, let's run the preview of it.
So, this was this was something that I
spun up. um uses AI to
generate business ideas, niches, scans
coaching trends, things like this,
market opportunities,
puts them together, and creates
uh different outputs and stuff like
that. So, which is which is pretty cool.
I'm not sure if it's actually linked up
with the AI to be able to do this
anymore, but I put this together by
simply just prompting it of what I
wanted to do with that. And so, Replet
is a really cool tool. I don't think
it's fully linked together to be able to
do that, but it's a really cool tool to
be able to put together these different
types of things. Okay, so this is going
right here. We're going to say build the
entire app. So, we're going to tell it
to just go build the whole thing
autonomously, and it's going to create
us the functionality of a Super Mario
Brothers clone right there, which is
pretty cool, which is awesome.
So, I'm going to show you an example of
when you're using one of these apps to
create this is couple of times you'll
you're not going to get the
functionality that you want. Um, I've
never seen it where just one prompt gets
that functionality. But what you do is
that you can take a screenshot of okay,
this isn't working. This says that the
game should be working. It's just a blue
screen and whatever you're creating does
this. And I just say it's still not
working when I press start. and the
agent will literally go to work to
figure out, okay, what's happening to
solve the problem and it will then
rewrite the code until it solves it.
Now, and one of the best hacks for this
that you can do is you just create a new
chat window that starts a new chat. It
opens it up. And so, you can see right
here, just by doing that, it's starting
to create the world for Mario type of
the thing that it's creating. And this
is this applies if you're creating an AI
app, if you're creating a tool that you
can use in your business and things like
that. This is a really great platform
for being able to put together and
prototype simple ideas that you have
that you could then put out there and
even sell as tools. You could create
something that can do stuff with
graphics or videos or anything like that
that's out there to be able to create
ideas.
A lot of these app builders have a
functionality where you can go in and
you can actually give it more autonomy
to be able to come up with ideas and go
deeper into it. You can actually
increase the level of of the power of
the AI model that it's using. Now, will
it cost a little bit more? Yeah. How is
the cost incurred? The cost is incurred
by how many prompts that you do and then
how much it has to work and then it it
comes up with the time that it's working
and then it starts to it'll charge you
based on that. So like for a simple app
like this it might cost you $15$20 to be
able to do that. But that's because it's
working through multiple different
prompts and doing this type of a thing
autonomously and automatically to be
able to put stuff like that together.
So, all that to say, again, these tools
are incredible for being able to put
together and prototype ideas that you
could create anything with and make them
live for people to play with.
Okay. And so, some of the functionality
is coming through here. You can see a
little bit there's like a bouncing
character, not fully working still, but
we're having the agent go through and
test it out. And this is what happens
when you're using one of these apps is
that it's not the functionality is not
always going to work out, but it gets
you to that place where it's going to
start to build it for you. Let's see
kind of what the agent can do as I start
to debug it and tell it what the problem
is. I went ahead and created kind of
another version of this instead of
another app right here. And so you can
kind of see how like functionality like
this might work where you have the
different graphics and the tools and
things like this that are moving forward
to create something like that. So again,
it's not perfect. And by the way,
creating a video game is a lot harder
than creating something that's like an
AI tool that can edit photos or or or
write sales copy or things like that or
an agent. But this shows you how you can
use AI to come up with different
concepts, prototype different things,
and put them out there to play around
with them. And so check some of these
out. Check out Replet. check out um
tools like that. If you want to go even
deeper into the code, you can even check
out a tool like cursor.sh.
This is a full-on um platform on your
computer for writing code and using AI
to do this very advanced stuff, but this
can do a lot of that for you. And so
that's what I just wanted to share with
you in this episode is how you can do
that, how you can put it together, how
you can see the results from it, and how
cool that is. Now, at the end of this,
we're going to show you kind of how once
I got Replet working right here, but I
just kind of wanted to wrap this up.
We're going to I'm going to show you the
results in just a second. I'm going to
might have to record it a little bit
later cuz I got to go do something else.
Uh, but we're going to come back to this
and you can see how this works and comes
together. All right, so I'm back. I came
back to show you the end of this. We let
Replet go ahead and use its AI agent to
process through making the
functionalities work and adding graphics
even to it. And the final result is
actually rather impressive. Um once it
starts working, understand that this is
a normal part of currently the way that
AI works in using these tools. This will
improve over time as technology gets
better. This is an early iteration of
this technology and I'm still majorly
impressed with what happens and what has
become of it and the results from it.
And so I'm going to show you this right
here.
This is our little character right here.
And if you use
the keyboard, I can use the keyboard and
I can jump him up here. He can grab
coins. That changes the the score
right there.
Look, here's a little uh little enemy
right here. So, we can jump on the
enemy. Okay, we got a got a point there.
Don't want to die.
Look at that. So, this was coded
entirely
using
uh replet agent right here. Now, it
doesn't have like an ending. it doesn't,
you know, it doesn't go uh completely
forever. So, that's one thing. One
improvement that we could add over time
is kind of adding an ending to it where
where it might go. But, you can see
right there, just like the idea of a
Super Mario game. Um, the AI literally
coded all of this. It created all the
files, all of the code, everything was
created to
build this out and for this to actually
function and actually work. And so it's
it's really quite
remarkable
what was able to be created
using a tool like Replet like this. And
this is just one example
of
what you can do with a tool like Replet
to be to be able to
take your ideas and turn them into
something that's truly remarkable and
valuable. You can use tools like cursor.
You can use uh you know, you can even
prototype stuff in in tools like PO or
things like that. All the different
tools that I've shown you in this video.
It's it's really remarkable. So listen,
if you want to know about marketing your
business, about marketing your products,
your apps, your services, my Wealthy
Coach Academy program is all about that.
Make sure to jump in there, try it out,
and see the difference that it makes
getting clients for you and your
business. All right, we'll talk soon.
Grow your life, everybody. Have a good
one.
[Music]
[Applause]